Guide to the Arthur Levitt, Jr. Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Speeches Background Material
  - Subseries IV.2: Various speakers
    - Thatcher, Margaret Prime Minister, UK, Nov. 12, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Thomas, Barbara S. US SEC, Jun. 1981 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Tolley, Joseph C. Apr. 25, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Vitullo-Martin, Julia Fiscal Observer, Nov. 19, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Walker, James W., Jr. SIA (Exec. VP), Mar. 24, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Wriston, Walter B. Citicorp, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Zises, Alvin, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Subseries IV.3: Drafts and Background Information
    Speech drafts, notes, printed material, quotes, memos etc used as background for speeches. Arranged by subject.
    - Drafts and Notes, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Capital Formation 1977 - 1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Clippings 1978 - 1988 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - The Executive Speaker 1982 - 1987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Small Business 1979 - 1981 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Securities Industry Association 1990 - 1993 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Printed Materials 1975 - 1985 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Quotes and correspondence 1973 - 1990 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Series V: Biographical
  Contains materials from Levitt's school years, pre-sec employment,TV appearances, honors.
  - Poly Prep School - Diary, 1945 - 1947 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Poly Prep School Yearbook, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Biographical Information, 1967 - 1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - American Stock Exchange, 1978 - 2000 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Hamilton College Arthur Levitt Public Affairs Center, 1981 - 1998 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Peterson, Peter; Levitt, Arthur; Weiss, Stanley BENS METRO Seminar, Feb. 20, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Moscovitch, Edward New England Economic Review The Downturn in the New England Economy: What Lies Behind It, with related correspondence, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Roll Call, 1990 - 1995 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Fields, Jack; Klein, Martin I.; Lang, Robert Todd; McLucas, William R.; Seligman, Joel Speeches of others about A. Levitt, 1994 - 2000 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - National Securities Clearing Corporation (NSCC); Depository Trust Company (DTC) Report of the Vision 2000 Committee, Sep. 1994 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Zanford, Charles Zanford vs. Levitt Case, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Awards, 1996 - 2002 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Wall Street Week with Louis Rukeyser, No. 2940, Mar. 31, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Series VI: Printed Materials
  - Subseries VI.1: Periodicals and broshures
    These materials were part of additions, donated by A. Levitt in 2002. They represent contents of original scrapbooks, created by A. Levitt. Materials are in original chronological order.
    - Periodicals and broshures, 1979 - 2001 (Box 23, Folder 1 - 5)
  - Subseries VI.2: News Clippings
    - Scrapbooks, 1965 - 2001 (Box 23A, Folder 1 - 6)
      [Materials represent contents of original scrapbooks, created by A. Levitt. Materials are in original chronological order. Correspondence and photographs from scrapbooks are replaced by photocopies, and the originals are moved to the corresponding series.]
    - SEC Resignation Letters and Clippings scrapbook, 2000 - 2001 (Box 23A, Folder 7)
    - After SEC Resignation, 2001 - 2002 (Box 23A, Folder 8)
    - Articles by A. Levitt Jr., 1977 - 1990 (Box 23A, Folder 9)
    - American Stock Exchange, Roll Call Articles re: A. Levitt Jr., 1977 - 1991 (Box 23A, Folder 10)
    - Articles sent by A. Levitt Jr. to son A. Levitt III, 1990 - 1991 (Box 23A, Folder 11)
    - Various clippings, 1988 - 1991 (Box 23A, Folder 12)
- Series VII: Arthur Levitt Sr. Papers
  Papers relating to father, NY State Comptroller Arthur Levitt Sr. See Audiovisual - Photos and Audio subseries for audiovisual materials related to A. Levitt Sr.
  - Correspondence, 1976 - 1980 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Speeches and Biography, 1963 - 1979 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials, 1977 - 1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Weinstein, Jack B. A Modern Constitution for New York, Syracuse, NY, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - NY State Comptroller Studies on Issues in Public Finance, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - US Treasury Bill Covering Guarantees of NYC Bonds, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Public Hearing on NY State Public Employee Pensoin Fund Investment Practices, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Columbia University, 1975 - 1979 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Green, S. William US House of Representatives Service Academy Selection Committee, 1979 - 1980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Excerpts from Speeches at Hamilton College, 1968 - 1995 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - A. Levitt Sr. Materials in New York State Archives, 1955 - 1978 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - NY State Comptroller News Clippings, 1971 - 1978 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Series VIII: Audiovisual Records
  Series consists of 115 VHS tapes and 9 Audiotapes. Arranged Chronologically. Duplicate tapes are at the end of the series
  - Subseries VIII.1: Video
    - Sub-subseries VIII.1.1: Hearings and Testimonies.
      21 unique VHS (24 total) tapes
      - Senate Confirmation Hearings, US SEC Chairman Arthur Levitt, [1993], (1 ) (Box 25, Folder 1)
        [2 duplicates]
      - Telecommunication and Finance Hearing. The Municipal Securities Market - Chairman Levitt, Sep. 9, 1993, (1 ) (Box 25, Folder 2)
        [1 duplicate]
      - Hearing on Mutual Fund Industry, Nov. 10, 1993, (1 ) (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations, Committee of Energy and Commerce, Concerning Bank Sales of Mutual Funds, Parts 1 - 4, Mar. 3, 2994, (4 ) (Box 25, Folder 4 - 7)
      - Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance. Chairman Levitt - Securities Regulatory Equality Act, Apr. 13, 1994, (1 ) (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - H. R. 3447, Panel # 2, Apr. 14, 1994, (1 ) (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Chairman's Hearing, Parts 1 - 2, May 25, 1994, (2 ) (Box 25, Folder 10-11)
      - Hearing before House Energy & Commerce Committee, Telecommunication and Finance Subcommittee on Securities Fraud Litigation with Arthur Levitt., Jul. 22, 1994, (1 (RT: 2 hrs. 8 min. 23 sec.) ) (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Rogue Brokers, Rep. Markey, Sep. 14, 1994, (1 ) (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, Jan. 5, 1995, (1 (RT: 3 hrs. 22 min.) ) (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - H. R. 10, Feb. 10, 1995, (2 ) (Box 26, Folder 2 - 3)
      - H. R. 10 Fields, Feb. 10, 1995, (1 ) (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - H. R. 18, Mar. 15, 1995, (2 ) (Box 26, Folder 5 - 6)
      - Subcommittee on Capital Market, Mar. 30, 1995, (1 ) (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Testimony before the Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance and the Subcommittee on Commerce, Trade and Hazardous Material. Arthur Levitt, Chairman, US SEC, Regarding H. R. 1062 The Financial Services Competitiveness Act of 1995, Jun. 6, 1995, (1 ) (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Sub-subseries VIII.1.2: Speeches and media appearances
      Series consists of 88 unique tapes (93 total)
      - American Electronics Association: Stock Options Rally, n.d., (1 ) (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Arthur Levitt, Jr.: A Man For All Seasons, n.d., (1 ) (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - American Association of Retired Persons: SEC Advice VNR, n.d., (1 ) (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Coastline Community College: Dollars & Sense. Program 119: Stocks., n.d., (1 ) (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - WFSB-TV (CBS); WTIC-TV (FOX) Connecticut Investors' Town Meeting, n.d., (1 ) (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - The Fight to Expose: The Blinder Robinson Scandals, n.d., (1 ) (Box 27, Folder 1)
        [Denver-based Blinder Robinson & Co.the largest penny stock brokerage in the country, filed for bankruptcy in 1990. The company's founder, Meyer Blinder, was convicted of securities fraud racketeering and money laundering two years later.]
      - US SEC How to Invest Wisely, n.d., (1 ) (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Levitt News Highlights, (1 ) (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Levitt on CNBC, n.d., (1 ) (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - National Press Club, n.d., (1 ) (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - US SEC New York Town Meeting by Crosswalks TV, n.d., (1 ) (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - PBS Newshour with Jim Lehrer: Full Disclosure, n.d., (1 ) (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - PBS Nightly Business Report: Chairman Levitt on Mutual Funds, n.d., (1 ) (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - PBS Nightly Business Report: Levitt Story, n.d., (1 ) (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - WNBC-TV (NBC) Nightly News: Wall Street Journal Scandal, Apr. 18, n.y., (1 ) (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Office of Thrift Supervision Seminar: Facing the Year 2000 Challenge Together, n.d., (1 ( RT: 57 min.) ) (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Philadelphia District Office: Jonathan Lebed, n.d., (1(RT: 10 min.) ) (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Shareholders Rights / Accounting Wrongs, n.d., (1 (RT: 7 min.) ) (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Bowne; Northeast Chapter for the American Corporate Counsel Association Think Twice 2: How the SEC Detects and Pursues Insider Trading, n.d., (1 ) (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - A Time for Justice, n.d., (1 ) (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Tuesday Morning General Session. Speaker: Arthur Levitt, n.d., (1 (RT: 31 min. 12 sec.) ) (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - PBS Wall Street Week # 748, n.d., (1 ) (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - City Club: Arthur Levitt, Jr., 1981, (1 ) (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - CNN Pinnacle with Arthur Levitt, Mar. 17, 1984, (1 ) (Box 28, Folder 6)
        [Tape also contains: Pinnacle with Deborah Szekely, Apr. 22, 1989]
      - ABC Good Morning America: Arthur Levitt, Dec. 1, 1986, (1 ) (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - CNN Inside Business: Arthur Levitt, Dec. 13, 1987, (1 ) (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - NBC Meet the Press: Arthur Levitt, Oct. 16, 1988, (1 ) (Box 28, Folder 9)
        [One of the tapes also contains: Cardinal O'Conner's Visit (FOX, Channel 5). 1 Duplicate]
      - US SEC Swearing In Video, [1993], (1 ) (Box 28, Folder 10)
        [Chairman's copy]
      - PBS Nightly Business Report: Chairman Levitt on Fund Managers, Jan. 11, 1994, (1 ) (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - PBS Morning Business Report: Chairman Levitt on Mutual Fund, Personal Trading, Jan. 12, 1994, (1 ) (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - ABC Good Morning America: Arthur Levitt, May 20, 1994, (1 ) (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Enforcement Roundtable Discussion, Jun. 13, 1994, (1 ) (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Bloomberg L. P. The Bloomberg Forum: SEC Chairman Arthur Levitt Interview, Aug. 29, 1994, (1 ) (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - CNN Moneyline: SEC Budget, Oct. 4, 1994, (1 ) (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Security Industry Association Annual Convention, Nov. 30 - Dec. 3. 1994. Day Three Module, [1994], (1 ) (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - CNBC Inside Opinion: Chairman Levitt on Mutual Funds, Mar. 31, 1995, (1 ) (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - WFAA-TV Investors' Town Meeting: SEC Chairman Arthur Levitt Appearance, Dallas, TX, Apr. 12, 1995, (1 ) (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - WFAA-TV Arthur Levitt SEC Air Check, Dallas, TX, Apr. 16, 1995, (1 ) (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - National Association of Securities Dealers NASD Annual Conference: Arthur Levitt speech on Broker Practices, May 19, [1994/1995], (1 ) (Box 29, Folder 8)
        [Year is 1995 on spine, 1995 on front label - Verify. Beninning of speech is missing.]
      - PBS Wall Street Week with Louis Rukeyser. Guest: Arthur Levitt, Jr., Jun. 9, 1995, (1 ) (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - WNET-TV (PBS); Merrill Lynch Wall Street Week: Chairman Arthur Levitt., Jun. 10, 1996, (1 ( RT: 11 min.) ) (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - GMA; CNBC Profile Prospectus, July 31, 1995, (1 ) (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - WJLA-TV (ABC) Good Morning America: Arthur Levitt / SEC and Mutual Funds, Washington, DC, July 31, 1995, (1 (RT: 1 hr. 45 min.) ) (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Government Finance Officers Association (GFOA); National Association of Counties (NACo) A Whole New Ballgame in Municipal Bond Disclosure, 1995, (1 (RT: 85 min. 14 sec.) ) (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Stanford Law School Executive Education Programs - Directors' College. Keynote Speech by Arthur Levitt., Mar. 1996, (1 ) (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - PBS; Alvin H. Perlmutter, Inc. Adam Smith Show # 1223: Arthur Levitt: A Conversation, Apr. 18, 1996, (1 (RT: 26 min. 46 sec.) ) (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - EdwardJones Regional Leader Meeting: Arthur Levitt, SEC Chairman, Apr. 21-23, 1996, (1 ) (Box 30, Folder 3)
        [Note on label: For internal use only. Do not show to the Public.]
      - C-SPAN Philadelphia Investors' Town Meeting, Philadelphia, PA, Jun. 11, 1996, (1 ) (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - National Association of Securities Dealers NASD Press Conference, Aug. 8, 1996, (1 ) (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - CNN-TV; Video Monitoring Services of America Moneyline: Arthur Levitt, Dec. 26, 1996, (1 (RT: 5 min. 23 sec.) ) (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - TV Footage on Arthur Levitt in Israel (KDH Ceremony), [1996], (1 ) (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - LA Times I.S.C: Arthur Levitt, Mar. 1997, (1 ) (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Detroit Economic Club Luncheon Talk. Hon. Arthur Levitt, SEC Chairman: CPA and CEO's - A Relationship at Risk, Detroit, MI, May 19, 1997, (1(RT: 51 min. 45 sec.) ) (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Bloomberg L. P. The Bloomberg Forum: SEC Chairman Arthur Levitt Interview, Jul. 30, 1997, (1 ) (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - CNBC Arthur Levitt in the news, May 27, 1997; May 6, 1998; Jul. 13, 1998, (1 ) (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - US SEC Summary of Investor Education Campaign (Informese Es Su Dinero Es Su Futuro), Chile, May 1, 1998, (1 (RT: 5 min.) ) (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Court TV Arthur Levitt Interview, Jun. 19-21, 1998, (1 ) (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - CNBC Arthur Levitt on Broker Pay, Jul. 13, 1998, (1 ) (Box 31, Folder 1)
        [Tape also contains: CNBC - John Stark on Internet Fraud, Jul. 13, 1998]
      - FOX News Channel Cavuto Report, Sep. 28, 1998, (1 ) (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - NBC; CNBC Nightly News: Arthur Levitt on Mutual Funds; Levitt on Mutual and Hedge Funds, Oct. 13-14, 1998, (1 (2 segments) ) (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - CNBC Hedge Fund Regulation, Oct. 15, 1998, (1 ) (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - William O. Douglas, Commission Meeting Room Dedication, Oct. 16, 1998, (1 ) (Box 31, Folder 5)
        [Note on label Master]
      - CNN Moneyline: Arthur Levitt, Oct. 30, 1998, (1 ) (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Bloomberg L. P. The Bloomberg Forum: SEC Chairman Arthur Levitt Interview, Nov. 18, 1998, (1 ) (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - [US SEC] Confirmation, 1998, (1 ) (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - [US SEC] Swearing In, 1998, (1 ) (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - CNN Arthur Levitt on Social Security, Feb. 17, 1999, (1 ) (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - [ABC News] Nightline, Mar. 2, 1999, (1 ) (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - PBS Wall Street Week with Louis Rukeyser. Guest: Arthur Levitt, Jr., #2837, Mar. 12, 1999, (1 ) (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - CNBC Arthur Levitt, Apr. 1999, (1 ) (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - National Press Club Luncheon - Arthur Levitt, May 4, 1999, (1 ) (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - CNBC Business Center: Phil Gramm, Sep. 28, 1999, (1 ) (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - NBC Fleecing of America: Arthur Levitt on Investment Advises Fraud., Nov. 17, 1999, (1 ) (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Remarks by Chairman Arthur Levitt, US SEC, Nov. 20, 1999, (1 ) (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - PBS Nightly Business Report: Arthur Levitt, Jan. 11, 2000, (1 ) (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - PBS Nightly Business Report: Arthur Levitt Interview, Jan. 17, 2000, (1 ) (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - PBS Wall Street Week with Louis Rukeyser: Arthur Levitt, Mar. 31, 2000, (1 ) (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - CNBC The Squawk Box: Arthur Levitt, SEC, May 10, 2000, (1 [RT: 6 min. 48 sec.] ) (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Investing for Success: Interview with Hugh Price, May 12, 2000, (1 ) (Box 32, Folder 9)
        [Note on label: No cutaways]
      - CBS 60 Minutes: Jonathan Lebed and Arthur Levitt, Oct. 22, 2000, (1 ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - PBS Wall Street Week with Louis Rukeyser: 30th Anniversary, # 3018, Nov. 3, 2000, (1 ) (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - North American Securities Administrators Association Annual Meeting of NASAA: SEC Chairman Arthur Levitt, Sep. 2000, (1 (RT: 12 min) ) (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - SEC Chairman Arthur Levitt: Retirement Message, Dec. 20, 2000, (1 ) (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - PBS, MPT Wall Street Week with Louis Rukeyser: First 30 Years, 2000, (1 (RT: approx 60 min.) ) (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - CBS 60 Minutes II - Roel of TV Analysts, Jan. 20, 2001, (1 ) (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Fairfield University, 51st Commencement Exercises, Class of 2001 - Awards, Honorary Degree Recepients, Addresses, Fairfield, CT, May 20, 2001, (1 ) (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Economic Club of Chicago The Greening of American Enterprise, Chicago, IL, Feb. 13, 1980, (1 ) (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Financial Management Network 1. Arthur Levitt Speaks out; (segment 1 - FEI and IMA news) 2. Corporate Governance and Financial Executives. 3. Business strategy and sales taxes. 4, Cash Flow in hard times., Nov. 2002 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Subseries VIII.2: Audio
    - Sub-subseries VIII.2.1: Arthur Levitt Jr.
      - NPR Consumer Initiative, Oct. 20, 1994, (1 side ) (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Prime Time Radio: Investing Information in Plain English, Mar. 11, 1997, (1/2 side ) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Symposium on Career Options For Minority Students in the Securities and Commodity Futures Industries, Feb. 19, 1998, (2 tapes (3 sides) ) (Box 34, Folder 3 - 4)
      - NPR Market Structure, Dec. 21, 1999, (1 side ) (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - LA Times Keynote: Tech Stock All-Stars: Top Fund Managers Give Picks, n.d., (1 side ) (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - US SEC Public Funds, Public Trust and the Federal Securities Laws, Alexandria, VA, n.d., (1 side ) (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Economic Club of Chicago Take on Wall Street, Chicago, IL, Oct. 15, 2002, (2 sides ) (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - unmarked tape, (2 tapes ) (Box 34, Folder 9 - 10)
    - Sub-subseries VIII.2.2: Arthur Levitt Sr.
      vinyl records, 10'' LP, 33 1/3 rpm. These materials were part of additions, donated by A. Levitt in 2002.
      - Talk by Hon. Arthur Levitt, Rochester, NY, Apr. 23, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 11)
        [78 needle ]
      - NBC-TV Citizens Union Searchlight, Oct. 25, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - WNEW-TV Metropolitan Probe, Jan. 10, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - CBS Let's Find Out, Jan. 31, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - WBAI Albany Report, Feb. 11, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - WNTA-TV Between the Lines, Feb. 14, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - WMCA Barry Gray Show, Mar. 19, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - WNEW Compulsory Fall-out Shelters, Mar. 20, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Subseries VIII.3: Photographs
    - Sub-subseries VIII.3.1: Arthur Levitt Jr.
      These materials were part of additions, donated by A. Levitt in 2002. Arthur Levitt in all pictures
      - Berlind, Roger S.; Ball, […]; Cogan, Marshall S.; Courter, James Andrew; Levitt family; Sturat, […]; Weill, Sanford I.; American Stock Exchange; Brandeis University; Defense Base Closure Commission; Hayden, Stone; Pre-SEC photos, v.p., 1967 - 1993, (6 8x10 b&w print, 3 8x10 color print, 1 5x7 color prints) (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Carter, Jimmy; Clinton, Bill; Clinton, Hillary Rodham; Gore, Albert; Reagan, Ronald; White House, Washington, DC, 1980 - 1999, (13 8x10 color print, 1 4x6 color print) (Box 34, Folder 20)
        [Photos contain signatures and autographs by Carter, Reagan, Clinton, Gore]
      - Block, Herbert; Dinkins, David; Photos with New York City Mayor David Dinkins, New York, NY, Aug. 18, 1993, (2 8x10 b&w print) (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Carey, […]; Hunt, [Isaac C.]; Johnson, […]; Schuetze, Walter P.; Turner, Lynn E.; Unger, Laura; SEC Staff, Washington, DC, n.d., (4 8x10 color print) (Box 34, Folder 22)
        [Photo by Greenfeld-Sanders, Timothy]
      - Dingell, John D. Boston Globe, New York Times; Washington Post Newspaper Photos of SEC chairman, v.p., n.d., (2 8x10 color print, 1 8x10 b&w print) (Box 34, Folder 23)
        [Washington Post photo inscribed to Levitt by John Dingell]
      - Brodsky, William J; Goldsberry, John W.; Goldsberry, William; Hartmann, Ulrich; Luthringshausen Wayne P.; Petzel, Todd; Sandner, Jack; Tully, Daniel P.; American Stock Exchange, Chicago Board Options Exchange; Chicago Mercantile Exchange; Merrill Lynch & Co; National Association of Securities Dealer; New York Stock Exchange, North American Securities Administration Association; Securities Industry Association; VEBA AG Industry Leaders, Chicago, IL; New York, NY, 1993 - 1998, (4 4x6 color print, 6 8x10 color print, 1 8x10 b&w print) (Box 34, Folder 24)
        [Copies of related correspondence enclosed. CBOE photos by Richard Shay,]
      - Rukeyser, Louis Maryland Public Television [Wall Street Week], [MD], 1995, (11 8x10 color print) (Box 34, Folder 25)
        [Inscription by Rukeyser (2 prints). Photos by Susan Noonan]
      - Gore, Albert; Swearing In for the 2nd SEC term, 1998, (6 4x6 color print) (Box 34, Folder 26)
        [Copy of the letter to Mr. Charles Burson of Apr. 29, 1998 re: swearing in.]
      - George Washington University; Hofstra University Universities, Washington, DC; Hempstead, NY, n.d., (8 8x10 color print) (Box 34, Folder 27)
        [Hofstra Photos by Brian Ballweb, Garden City, NY]
      - Cameron, Alan Australian Securities and Investment Commission Trips - Australia, n.p., n.d., (3 5x7 b&w prints, 1 5x7 color prints) (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Trips - Egypt, Egypt, n.d., (4 5x7 color prints) (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - Arnon, Igai; Karet, […]; [Netanyahu, Benjamin]; Nissim, Moshe; Ofir, […]; Ronel, Shalon Israel Securities Authority Trips - Israel, Israel, [1994], (7 5x7 color prints) (Box 34, Folder 30)
        [Invitation in Hebrew enclosed. Photos by Sarit Uziely]
      - Securities and Futures Commission Trips - Hong Kong, Hong Kong, [2000], (2 5x7 color prints, 3 4x6 color print, 5 4x5 color print) (Box 34, Folder 31)
        [Copy of the letter from Andrew Sheng of Jul. 31, 2000 enclosed]
      - Public Education / Dallas Town Meeting., v.p., n.d., (2 8x10 b&w print, 3 5x7 color prints) (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - American Bar Association; Anti-Defamation League Associations, [1997], (4 5x7 b&w prints, 2 4x6 color print) (Box 34, Folder 33)
        [Copy of letter from Salomon Brothers' Simon M. Lorne enclosed]
      - Various Photographs, (4 8x10 color print, 5 5x7 color prints, 5 5x7 b&w prints, 1 8x10 b&w print, 5 4x6 color prints and smaller) (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Sub-subseries VIII.3.2: Arthur Levitt Sr.
      - Photos of A. Levitt, Sr., (8 b&w, 1 color) (Box 34, Folder 35)
      - Mark Bomse Contact Sheets of A. Levitt, Sr., (9 b&w) (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - Faximile of signatures of various politicians, including A. Levitt, NY State Comptroller (Box 34, Folder 37)
- Series IX: Digital Materials
  These materials were part of additions, donated by A. Levitt in 2002.
  - Selected Releases from the SEC Website, www.sec.gov, prepared by chairman A. Levitt, Sep. 1995 - Jan. 2001, (CD-R) (Box 34, Folder 38)
    [primarily .html and .pdf files]
  - Janelle Haskell Prime Time Radio; AARP Arthur Levitt (tracks 1 and 2), Oct. 15, 2002, (30:06 audio CD) (Box 34, Folder 39)
- Series X: SEC Work Files
  All files in this series were part of additions, donated by A. Levitt in 2002. Original titles. General SEC subject files are followed by subseries arranged alphabetically by office of origin or subject.
  - Subseris X.1: General
    - SEC Annual Reports, 1993 - 1999 (Box 35, Folder 1 - 4)
    - Legislative developments affecting SEC, 1993 - 2000 (Box 35, Folder 5 - 6)
    - SEC Press Releases Index, 1993 - 2000 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - SEC Rules - proposed and final, 1993 - 2001 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Press Statements by Levitt, 1993 - 2000 (Box 36, Folder 1)